（男鹿）((オレと
つきあってください))
Will you do it with me?
（邦枝　葵）《妙な男だったわね》
What a strange fellow...
≪あうぁ！≫
それじゃあ光太　行ってくるね。
Well then, Kota... I'm heading out now.
（光太）あい～！あいあい！
（寧々）おはようございま～す。
葵姐さん。→
'Morning, Madame Aoi!
で　例の男鹿辰巳の件ですが…。→
Now, about this Oga Tatsumi
and the trouble he's caused...
２年の阿部　下川　真田兄弟→
The second years Abe, Shimokawa,
and the Sanada Brothers,
そして３年の神崎　姫川を→
plus the third years Kanzaki and Himekawa...
全て一撃で倒すほどの
凶暴さだそうです。→
It seems he is so violent he
defeated them all in one hit.
そして奇妙なことに
いつも背中には…。
And for some strange reason,
always on his back is a...
どちらにせよ　石矢魔の女子を
脅かす可能性のあるヤツには…。
It matters not. Anyone who might pose
a threat to the women of Ishiyama...
私が鉄槌を下す！
I will bring the iron hammer down upon them!
相変わらず　見事な腕前っすね！
Your technique is impressive, as always!
待ってなさい！男鹿辰巳！
Just you wait, Oga Tatsumi!
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんな事から
赤ん坊を育てる事になった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語＞
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
＜ただし　その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです！＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
We Met Again
（男鹿）どうだ？うまいか？
So? Tasty?
（ベル坊）ダーッ！
（ヒルダ）だいぶ手慣れてきた
ようだな。良いことだぞ。
You've quite gotten the hang
of it. That's excellent.
ハラ減るたびに泣かれて
感電してりゃあ→
After getting shocked each time he cries
because he's hungry, heck yeah I got the hang of it!
少しは慣れるだろうよ！
だいたい　こういうのは
女の仕事なんじゃねぇのか？
And isn't this a woman's job, anyway?
ほう？人間界は男女同権。→
Oh? Men and women have equal
rights in the human world.
今では男も積極的に育児に
参加するものだと聞いているが。
I hear that men are now playing
active roles in child-rearing.
よそはよそ！うちはうち！
（古市）≪お～が～く～ん！≫
That's out there! But this is my house!
Oga-kun!
ああ？
（古市）いっしょに学校いこ～！
お前は小学生か！
Let's go to school togethers!
What are you, 12?!
貴様　これまでも坊っちゃまを→
Until now, you have been trying to push
the master onto someone else, you fiend.
他人に押し付けようと
していたが…。
ギクッ！
坊っちゃまに
選ばれたのは強さの証。→
The master choosing you
is proof of your strength.
少しは誇りに思うのだな。
You should take some pride in that.
ぐ…。
（古市）は～や～く～！
Hurry ups!
うるせえ！
エッ！？
Shuddap!
えへ…ヘヘヘ～。
えらく上機嫌だな。
What're you on cloud nine for?
だってさぁ～
今日から帰ってくるんだぜ～。
Because the Queen has returned!
誰が？
Who?
女王だよ　石矢魔の女王！
The Queen! Ishiyama's Queen!
女王？
ダブ～？
Queen?
おい！あれ！
どうした？
Hey, look...
What is it?
スゲェよ　女子がいるぜ。
おほほ～！
Whoa! There are girls here!
（女子達の話し声）
おい　ちょっかい出してみろよ。
Hey, go try talkin' to 'em!
いや　お前いけよ。
遠慮すんなよ。
No-no, you go.
No need to be shy!
てめぇこそ遠慮すんなよ。
何だよ　ビビッてんのか？
There's no need for you to be shy either!
What, you scared?
何だと！？コラ！
やるか　コラ！
Say that again, punk!
You wanna go, huh?
（女子達）あっ！
（男子達）おお！？
（女子一同）おかえりなさいませ！
Welcome back!
あれは！？
That's...
北関東の　全レディース制圧から
帰ってきたのか！？
She's back after conquering
all the Ladies of North Kanto!
この石矢魔の女王…。
Our Ishiyama's Queen!
クイーン邦枝！
Queen Kunieda!
≪うわぁ　葵様≫
Queen Aoi!
≪寧々様も　前より
たくましくなられたみたい≫
And Nene-san looks even
more gallant than before!
≪千秋さん　相変わらずクール≫
Chiaki-san's just as cool as ever!
（女子達）あぁ～。
（古市）男鹿～！見てみろよ！
はぁ？
Oga, look at this!
（古市）女子！女子！女子！女子！
Girls! Girls! Girls! Girls!
石矢魔の女王が帰ってきたお陰で
このむさ苦しい石矢魔に→
Thanks to Ishiyama's Queen returning...
It's like late sakura are blooming
in this decrepit Ishiyama!
遅咲きの桜が
咲いたかのようじゃないか！
ふぅ～ん…お前も飲むか？
ダ～ブッ！
You want some?
男鹿！
あの女子の群れを見ても→
Oga! Even after looking
at that group of girls,
まだ　事の重大さが
わからないのか！？
you still don't understand
the gravity of the situation?
いや　だってうち　女子少ねえけど
もともと共学だろ？
Well, I know there aren't many girls, but
we're originally an integrated school, right?
そんな設定　誰も知らね～よ！
No one actually knew that!
つ～か　今まで男子校だと
思ってたヤツ→
Most people totally thought
this was an all-boys school!
多数ですよ！正味な話…。
Seriously!
寒かった…寒かったっすよ
アホな不良男子に囲まれて送る→
It was cold... Oh, so very cold...
My drab-gray colored high school life,
surrounded by idiotic male delinquents...
灰色学園生活…だが　しか～し！→
But, now...
これからは　違うぜ～！
Things are going to be different!
なあ男鹿！
恋しちゃっていいか～い！？
Say Oga... Is it okay for me to fall in love?
うぜえ…。
ブ…。
Ugh...
うおお！？これは美女の予感！
行くぞ～！
Ooh! My babe-sense is tingling!
Here we go!
おお！あれこそは…。
てめぇ　古市！
That's...
Hold it, Furuichi!
（砂ぼこりが舞う音）
（古市）
やや大柄だが　健康的なボディ！→
That quite large, solidly built body!
引き締まった尻！
どうだ　あの子は！？
That firm ass!
What do you think of her?
（アランドロン）ウフン！
古市殿　ここでしたか！
Furuichi-dono! There you are...
昼間　古市殿に会えない寂しさから
私も登校してみましたぞ！→
I was so lonely during the day not
being able to see you, Furuichi-dono,
so I've come to the school!
この制服　いかがですかな？
What do you think of my school uniform?
とにかく！その女子達の頂点に
立つってのが　石矢魔の女王→
Anyway, the person at the
pinnacle of all these girls,
is Ishiyama's Queen Kunieda!
クイーン邦枝なんだってよ！
クイーンねぇ…。
さあ　行くぞ！見にいくぞ！
すぐ行くぞ～！
Queen, huh?
So, let's go! Let's check
her out! Let's go now!
ダダダ…！髪引っぱるなって！
ダダダ…！
Don't pull my hair, damn you!
古市殿～！
Furuichi-dono!
オイ…オイ…オイ…。
おい　何だ　ありゃ？
Whoa. What the hell is that?
キモッ！
おっさんか？
Ew...
Some old guy?
うん？…パァッ！
帰ってきて早々　見廻りか？
Making the rounds so quick after your return?
お高く止まりやがって。
Get off yer high horse, girly!
≪スカート履けよ　スカート！≫
Put on a skirt, would ya?
相変わらず胸くそ悪いとこだねぇ。
These boys are always so annoying...
葵姐さん！ガツンと
いったりましょうよ！→
Madame Aoi, tell 'im who's boss!
ナメられたら　しまいっすよ！
Don't let them walk all over you!
ほっときなさい。
どうせ何も出来やしないわ。
Ignore them.
They don't actually have
the guts to do anything.
ちっ！
ムカつくぜ。
Now that pisses me off.
（阿部）オレにまかせときな。
Leave this to me!
（不良）キラーマシーン阿部！
（不良）何をキラーするんだ！？
It's Abe, the Killing Machine!
What're you gonna kill?
今日～のエモノは…アレだ～！
Today's prey is... there!
おお～っと！
なぜか　いきなり滑った～！
Whoops! I accidentally slipped!
えへへ…。
ヘヘェ。
ギエッ！？うおおお…！！
千秋　もうやめなさい。
死ぬから。
Chiaki, that's enough.
You're going to kill him.
≪う～ん　怖いねぇ≫
あ？
Ooh, how scary.
（下川）高圧で噴射された水は→
I had heard that highly pressurized
water blasts can even cut through metal,
金属すら切断できるって
いうけど→
間近で見ると恐ろしいねぇ。
あっ　グッナイ。
but actually seeing them in
action is quite frightful, yes.
Oh! Good night.
《こんなんばっか…》
Are they all like this?
今　朝だけど。
It's morning, though.
こいつは手厳しい。
で　例の件　考えてくれた？
That's just harsh of you.
So, have you thought about my deal?
何のことよ？
What do you mean?
約束だろ？君と戦って勝ったら
オレと付き合ってくれるって。
You promised, remember? If I fought
you and won, you'd go out with me.
ああ…。
Oh, yeah... I think I did
promise something like that.
《そういえば
そんな約束したっけ》
グッド　その表情　いいね。
（カシャ　カシャ…！）
Good. That's the look I like.
姐さんとやりたいんなら
まず　私を倒してからっす。
You wanna do it with her,
you gotta beat me first!
（下川）え～？いいけど　オレ
君とは付き合えないよ。
Fine, but I'm not going to date you, got it?
んな心配してねぇよ！キモ男！
寧々　やめなさい！
No need to worry about that, you freaky man!
Nene, quit it!
来な。３秒で　おやすみ
させてやるよ。グッナイ。
Come on. I'll put you out in three seconds.
Good night!
なら　こっちは１秒だよ。
Then I'll do you in one!
やめなさいって　言ってんでしょ。
I told you to quit it.
はい…。
っていうか　それ木刀だよね？
Wait... That's a wooden sword, right?
（千秋）おお～。
And?
で　私と戦って勝ったら…
だっけ？
You were saying something
about, "if you beat me"?
あ…うん　また今度ね。
グッナ～イ。
Uh, right... Maybe another time...
Good night!
ずげえ…。
木刀で　どうやったら…。
Whoa...
How did she do that with a wooden sword?
（古市）どこだ！どこなんだ！？
石矢魔のクイーンは～！
Where? Where is she?
Where's Ishiyama's Queen?
って…うわぁ～！
誰か…救急車…。
Someone... Call an ambulance...
こえ～っ　ケンカか？
なあ　オレ　そろそろベル坊に…。
Scary... Was there a fight?
Hey, I need to feed Baby Beel soon...
ここには　いないみたいだな。
ほら！次行くぞ　次！
いや　だから…。
It doesn't look like she's
here. On to the next!
But I'm trying to tell you...
ううぅ…ガクッ。
（美破）うふ　うふふ…→
鏡よ鏡　この石矢魔で
いちばん美しいのは　だぁ～れ？
Mirror, mirror in my hand, who is the
fairest in all the land of Ishiyama?
（碇）キキッ！ってことで
今日から登校らしいですよ。
Actually, it seems she's
come back to school now.
（美破）
相変わらず　空気読めないのね。
（碇）は？
Always breaking the mood, you are.
（美破）まあいいわ。
誰が登校ですって？
Whatever. Who came back to the school?
（碇）はい。石矢魔の女王こと
クイーン邦枝。
Right. Ishiyama's Queen, Kunieda.
（美破）何ですってぇ！？
（碇）アヒィ！
What did you say?!
（美破）もう一度聞くわよ！→
Let me ask you one more time...
鏡よ鏡　この石矢魔で
いちばん美しいのは！？
Mirror, mirror in my hand, who is the
fairest in all the land of Ishiyama?
（碇）ウキキ！
そ　それは美破様です…。
T-That would be you, Miwa-sama.
（美破）
うふふ　うふふふ…。
やっと空気読めたじゃないの。→
Well, it seems you finally
went with the mood.
この石矢魔に
女王は２人もいらないわ。
There isn't room for two
Queens in this school!
（碇）ウキキ…。
（美破）いいこと？徹底的に
邦枝　葵をマークしなさい→
Listen. I want you to keep tabs
on this Kunieda Aoi person.
あの女の行動の
一部始終を報告するのよ！
Report her every little activity!
（葵）ったく　売られたケンカ
全部買ったら→
If you accept every challenge to a fight
with you, there won't be any end to it!
キリないでしょ？
はい…。
Yes'm.
私たちの敵は　たった一人よ。
はい。
We only have one enemy.
Yes'm.
Tell me who it is.
（葵）誰だか言ってみなさい。
男鹿辰巳です。
Oga Tatsumi.
そうよ！
That's right!
While we were gone,
私たちのいない間に
校内破損１３件。→
there have been 13 incidents at the school
that sent more than 50 people to the hospital!
病院送り５０人以上。
１年生ながら　すでに２年生→
Even though he's a first year, he's already
taken on the second and even third years!
３年生をも　その手にかけた
悪魔のような男！
That man's like some sort of demon!
((ウハハハハ…！))
このままじゃ　石矢魔は
壊滅（かいめつ）すると言われているわ。はい…。
If things keep going like this,
Ishiyama will be demolished.
Right.
男子は　どうでもいいけど→
I don't care about the boys, but in order to
protect the girls from his poison claws...
女子達を　その毒牙から
守るためにも！
男鹿辰巳に鉄槌を下さなきゃいけないのよ！
We have to bring down the
iron hammer on Oga Tatsumi!
Right.
はい…。
《男鹿辰巳…どんな恐ろしい
相手だろうが　私が必ず！》
How fearful an opponent
must this Oga Tatsumi be?
I will definitely...
どこ～！？
クイーンどこなの～！？
Where? Where's the Queen?
Damn it, I can't find her!
くそっ　見つからねぇ～！
だいたい女王ったって
どうせ不良だろ？
いやいや！
You call her Queen, but she's
just a delinquent, right?
Oh, no... According to what I
hear, she's the perfect woman!
聞いた話じゃ
大和撫子らしいぞ！→
それに　この石矢魔の女子を→
And she protects the girls of
Ishiyama from the delinquents!
不良達の毒牙から
守ってるらしいぜ！
So you're the first one she'd skewer, right?
なら　お前が真っ先に
ブチのめされるな。
しかも　その強さは
あの姫川や神崎以上って噂だ！
And the rumors are that she's
stronger than Himekawa or Kanzaki.
へ～。
だ～。
（姫川）ヘーックション！
（神崎）ハックション！
フッ　風邪か？
誰か噂してやがるな。
A cold?
Someone was sayin' stuff about me.
それよりも　わかってるよなあ？
ああ…あの女王とやらが→
Anyway... You get the picture, right?
Yeah. We can't let that Queen get the
upper hand while she thinks we're gone.
俺達が居ないと思って
つけ上がらないよう…。
ガツンと一発！
釘を刺しとかねぇとな…。
Thwack her down hard. Gotta
keep the nails from poppin' up.
どわっ！！
神崎に姫川…
アンタら入院してたんじゃ？
Kanzaki and Himekawa...
Weren't you two in the hospital?
フッ　金の力で解決よ。
Money solved that.
それより　そこの姉ちゃんに
言いたい事があってなあ。
Anyway, we have something
to say to this lady here.
Oh, what?
へえ　何よ？
お　おい。
お前　言ってやれよ。
H-Hey...
You tell her.
あ？あ…あ…ゴホン！
Uh? Uh... Uh...
てめえ　わかってるだろうがなぁ！
俺達が居ない間にぃ！
You get the picture right?
While we're gone...
W-While we're gone...
お…俺達が居ない間に…
北関東制圧　お疲れ様です。
Good work in conquering North Kanto...
And... Welcome back!
いや　うん…お帰り。
何　あれ？
ほっときな　行くよ。
What was that?
Leave them alone.
Let's go.
《あんなザコは　どうでもいい。
それよりも　男鹿辰巳を…》
I don't care about those small fry.
More importantly, where's Oga Tatsumi?
Queen!
クイーン！
We need to feed Baby Beel his milk!
それより　ベル坊にミルクを…。
ダーッ！
おい！？
あれは！？
Hey...
Isn't that...
Hey! Where are you?
ねえ　どこにいるんです～っ！
Let's do it.
野郎…。
この間の　お礼参りと行くか。
It's time to pay him back, huh?
Where are you?
（古市）どこだ～！クイーン！
Queen!
After we heal up.
この傷が治ったら…だな。
ああ…。
Right?
Yes. Anyway, how about a banana?
それより　バナナ食うか？
うん　ちょうだい。
Sure. Thanks.
クイーン！
Queen!
いったい　どこに…。
Where in the world could he...
Queen!
クイーン！！
古市殿～！どこですか～っ！？
Furichi-dono! Where are you?
葵姐さん　このままじゃ→
Madame Aoi, nothing is going
to be settled at this rate.
埒が明きませんし　いったん…。
（古市）≪クイーン！≫
Queen!
Let us...
Give me a break here, okay?
そろそろ勘弁してくれ…。
What are you talking about, Oga?
You want to meet the Queen, right?
なに言ってんだ　男鹿。
クイーンに会いたいだろ！？
…あれは。
来た。
向こうから？
That's...
He's coming.
He came to us?
クイーン
姐さんに会いたいって？
You want to meet the Queen?
《ふふっ　なるほどね。→
I see.
After Kanzaki and Himekawa, I'm next, huh?
神崎　姫川と来て
次は私ってわけだ》
なめてくれるじゃない
男鹿辰巳！
You're underestimating me, Oga Tatsumi!
Prepare yourself!
覚悟なさい！
あんたの悪行も　ここまでよ！
Your evil ways end now!
な！？
（葵）ん？
んんん…！？
《うわ　もしかして…
これが邦枝葵！？》
Could this be Kunieda Aoi?
Ooh, nice! Navel exposure!
イイね！おへそ見えてるし！
あ　あ…あんたが　男鹿辰巳？
Y-You're Oga Tatsumi?
そ～だけど？
Yes. And...?
あの～めっちゃ見た事ある
顔なんですけど。
Um... I've totally seen him around before.
Look, over here!
（不良達）おい　こっちだ　こっち！
すげえぞ。
Whoa!
The Rampaging Ogre and Queen Kunieda
are going at it right off the bat!
子連れオーガとクイーン邦枝が
いきなり激突だってよ！
Seriously?
（不良達）マジかよ！？
一体　どっちが勝つんだ！？
Which one of 'em will win?
《どうする？幸い向こうは　まだ
気付いていないみたいだし→
What'll I do? Thankfully, he
doesn't seem to have realized yet.
とにかく　ここは
初対面のフリして…》
Anyway, I'll just pretend like
I've never met him before...
Could it be... He noticed?
《まさか　気付いてる！？》
ダッ　アイ！
Uh... He definitely knows!
《あの目！？間違いない
あの子は何か気付いてるわ！》
That kid has noticed something!
《いや　気のせいか…》
My imagination?
ダーッ！
《やっぱ気付いてる！？》
I knew it, he noticed!
ハフー。
《違うか…》
No?
He totally noticed!
ダーッ！
《めっちゃ気付いてる！？》
フー。
《違う？》
No?
ダーッ！！
《ど　どっち！？》
Which one is it?
Oga!
男鹿ぁ～っ！！
（葵）《こ　今度は何！？》
なんだよ。
What is it now?!
What?
見ろ…後ろの２人も
めっさレベル高いぞ。
もう帰っていいか？
Look! The two behind her are
serious keepers as well!
Can I go home now?
ちょ　おまっ！
何で　そ～なるんだよ！？
Come on, man! Why you gotta be like this?
The Queen called your name herself!
クイーン自ら
声をかけてくれてんだぞ！？
いや　完全に
ケンカ売られてたろ？
Well, it sounded like she's picking a fight.
《しかし　こいつ
高校生だったのね…→
But, he's in high school.
And wait, is the kid from some relationship?
てゆ～か　あの子は
出来ちゃった子ども？→
学校に連れてきてまで
面倒見てて…→
He takes care of him, even
taking him to school....
Is he really such a bad person?
本当に　そんなに
悪い奴なのかしら？》
おいおい　何やってんだ？
お見合いか？
Hey-hey! What're you doing?
Arranged marriage?
You ain't scared, right?
ビビッたんじゃね～の？
女王っつっても→
You're called the Queen, but
in the end you're just a woman!
所詮は女か
その程度かよ　邦枝。
Is that all you got, Kunieda?
あ　葵姐さん…。
くっ…。
Madame Aoi?
（葵）はっ！
（バリバリ…）
Put down the baby.
（葵）赤ん坊を降ろしなさい。
あ？
それじゃ　本気で闘えないでしょ？
You can't fight seriously that way, right?
おいおい　木刀って
切れるもんなのか！？
Whoa, hold it... She cut
that with a wooden sword?
オーッ！
ベル坊？
Baby Beel?
ダーブッ！アイーッ！
((だいたい　こういうのは
女の仕事なんじゃね～のか？))
And isn't this a woman's job, anyway?
((坊っちゃまに選ばれたのは
強さの証))
The master choosing you
is proof of your strength.
お～っ！
オーッ！
ん？
いいぜ。
Good.
Oga?
男鹿？
来いよ　このまま相手してやる。
Come at me. I'll fight you like this.
お　おい！？
H-Hey!
男鹿辰巳
赤ん坊を盾にするだなんて→
Oga Tatsumi... Using a baby as a shield.
You really are a total bastard.
やっぱりクズ野郎だったのね…。
それとも…→
Or is it...
私のこと…→
...that you are...
ナメてんのかしら？
...underestimating me, perhaps?
He dodged!
（葵）《かわした？
まさか今の間合いで！？》
Even at this distance?
やるわね。
でも　ここまでです。
Not bad.
But, this will end it.
（寧々）ええ　出るわ…→
Yes... Here it comes.
新月流抜刀術　弐式。
その名も…→
Shingetsu sword school, second style.
Its name is...
百花　乱れ桜！
Countless Petals...
Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
ぐっ…おお　ぐっ！？
男鹿～っ！！
（不良達）うおお…！
Oga!
《ウソでしょ…》
You've got to be kidding me...
Scary! What are you, Hilda?
こえ～っ！ヒルダかよ？
He dodged them all!
（葵）《全部　かわしてる…》
（不良達）どっちも…すげえ…。
Both of them are amazing...
ダメだろ　校舎壊しちゃあ。
いや　お前の言う事じゃ…。
Now look what you did to
the school building...
Uh, you're not one to talk.
アーッ！アッ　アイー！
お～そうか　そうか。
Oh, right! You like her, huh?
やっぱ気に入ったか～。
よ～し　よしよし。
Okay, righty then.
そうだよなぁ。
女で　その上強いもんなぁ。
She's a woman, and she's strong too!
ダーブー！
待ってろ…。
Hold up a sec...
What power!
（葵）《なんて力！？殺られる…》
He's going to kill me!
Madame!
姐さん！
《殺るんなら　早く…》
If you're going to do it, get it over with...
こいつの…。
Take this...
...baby and be its mother, please?
母親になってくれませんか？
（一同）ああ…あ…。
…え？
Huh?
W-W-W-W-What are you saying?
なっ　なななっ！なに言ってんの！？
ブアッカじゃない！？
You're kidding, right?
Y-You big fat idiot!
あ～！もう　バーカ！
やる気なくなったじゃない！
I don't even wanna fight anymore!
I'll let you off for now.
今日は
この辺にしといてやるわ！
You stupid stupid-face, Oga!
バーカ　バーカ！男鹿のバーカ！
…また会いましょ！
あ　おい？
See you later, 'kay?
Ah... Oy!
（葵）あ　おい？
…あおい？葵！？
A... oi...?
Aoi?
Don't just call me by
my first name like that!
いきなり下の名前で呼ぶな～っ！！
You stupid jerk! You stupid,
stupid, stupid jerk!
バーカ！バカ　バカ　バカーッ！！
（寧々）姐さん！？
Madame, wait! Please wait, Madame Aoi!
待って下さいよ！葵姐さ～ん！
何だよ？
What was that?
はっはっはっはっ
探しましたぞ　古市殿！
また　いつの間に～！？
I was searching for you, Furuichi-dono!
When did you...
（アランドロン）あん～！
（古市）抱きつくなって～！！
Stay off of me!
（碇）キキキッ…。
That guy's the worst...
Using such cheap tactics.
ほんと　最低な奴でしたね。
卑怯な手　使いやがって！
動揺させようとしてんのが
見え見えなのよ。ねえ　千秋！
It's so obvious he was
just trying to get to you.
Isn't that right, Chiaki?
葵姐さん！あんな卑怯な手に
引っかからないで下さいよ！
Madame Aoi... Please, don't fall
for such dirty tricks, okay?
あ…姐さん？
Madame?
あいつ…バツイチなのかな…。
I wonder if he's divorced?
M-Madame Aoi!?
（寧々）あ　葵姐さあぁ～～ん！？
（美破）んふふふ…なるほど。→
I see... So Kunieda Aoi has
such a crucial weak-point...
邦枝葵にも
とんだ弱味があったものね。
（碇）キキッ！では　いよいよ
我々の出番ですね。
Then it's finally our turn, yes?
（美破）頼むわよ。
（碇）はい。必ずや　石矢魔の女王→
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
We will definitely take down
Ishiyama's Queen, Kunieda...
クイーン邦枝を…。
（美破）誰が女王ですってぇえ！？
Who did you call the Queen?
（碇）グホッ！
Next time, read the mood, okay?
（美破）次回こそは　ちゃんと
空気読みなさいよ！→
フフフフ…ハハハハ…！
Damn it all! Why is that
bastard Oga so popular?
He lives under the same roof as Hilda-san,
and now he's even being crushed on by the Queen!
W-When did I have a crush, huh?
Anyway, it seems like a bunch of people who
don't read the mood have started something.
I feel a storm coming...
On the next Beelzebub: Love is a Hurricane!
Anyway, are you sure this is gonna be okay?
This is seeming less and less like
an academy just full of delinquents.
W-We aren't all bad apples!